Finding aid of the Herbert Hutchinson Brimley Photograph Collection, 1880-1977 PHC.42
State Archives of North Carolina
- Sport Fishing, PhC.42.SprtFishing; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Topsail Inlet, Pender Co., NC, 1914. (25n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F36-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Brown's Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1915. (2), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F37-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Brown's Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1915. (2), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F37-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1917. (24n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F38-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-23; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-24; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-25; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-26; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-27; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Orton Pond, Brunswick Co., NC, 1920. (17) (9n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F39-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1920. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F40-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1920. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F40-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1920. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F40-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1920. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F40-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, New River Inlet, Onslow Co., NC, 1920. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F40-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Black bass fishing from horseback, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1908; Mountain fishing, 1915. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F41-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Black bass fishing from horseback, Avery Co., NC, ca. 1908; Mountain fishing, 1915. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F41-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Folder Catch of Bass, Currituck Co., NC, 1921. (PCD), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F42; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Boat fishing, Doctor's Lake, Wake Co., NC, 1926. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F43; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-17; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-18; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-19; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-20; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-21; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-22; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Onslow Fishing Club, Onslow Co., NC, 1927. (20) (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F44-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Wallace Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1929. (6n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F45-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Wallace Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1929. (6n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F45-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Wallace Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1929. (6n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F45-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Wallace Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1929. (6n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F45-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Wallace Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1929. (6n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F45-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Wallace Creek, Onslow Co., NC, 1929. (6n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F45-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-13; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-14; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-15; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-16; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - U.S. Fisheries Boat, Cape Lookout, NC, 1935. (8) (8n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F46-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Lake Phelps, Washington Co., NC, 1939. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F47; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fishing, Cape Lookout, NC, 1941. (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F48-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two fake fishing scenes, White Lake, NC, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F49; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two fake fishing scenes, White Lake, NC, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F50; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two fake fishing scenes, White Lake, NC, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F51; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Two fake fishing scenes, White Lake, NC, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F52; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fisherman w/ channel bass, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F53-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Fisherman w/ channel bass, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.SprtFishing.F53-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Structures, PhC.42.Structures; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, ca. 1907. (2) (N.76.9.7), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Wray family on the porch of Wray Villa, Yancey Co., NC, 1906. (N.76.9.4), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Model of an exotic bird aviary, London Zoo, 1961., PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified houses, buildings, and Monuments, PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Upchurch House on McDowell Street in Raleigh, NC, across from Nash Square next to Hotel Raleigh (where N&O buildings are now), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F4-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified beach houses, ca. 1920s. (1) (7n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F5-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Front porch, unidentified house, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.Structures.F6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Tools, PhC.42.Tools; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Ash hopper, High Falls, Moore Co., NC, 1930. (1) (n), PhC.42.Bx28.Tools.2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Home built cotton gin, ca. 1930s. (3), PhC.42.Bx28.Tools.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Home built cotton gin, ca. 1930s. (3), PhC.42.Bx28.Tools.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Home built cotton gin, ca. 1930s. (3), PhC.42.Bx28.Tools.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Transportation, PhC.42.Transport; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Railroad car and causeway, Wrightsville Beach, New Hanover Co., NC, 1913. (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.Transport.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Railroad car and causeway, Wrightsville Beach, New Hanover Co., NC, 1913. (2n), PhC.42.Bx28.Transport.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Automobile on an unpaved rural road, 1920s., PhC.42.Bx28.Transport.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered wagon pulled by mules, ca. 1900s., PhC.42.Bx28.Transport.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Transport.F4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Horse drawn buggies on rural roads in New Hanover County and Wake County, ca. 1903., PhC.42.Bx28.Transport.F5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
- Unidentified, PhC.42.Unidentified; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified children at play with a cart, ca. 1900s. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F1-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified children at play with a cart, ca. 1900s. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F1-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified children at play with a cart, ca. 1900s. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F1-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified children at play with a cart, ca. 1900s. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F1-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified children at play with a cart, ca. 1900s. (5n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F1-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified building, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Unidentified house and street, n.d. (n), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-1; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-10; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-11; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-12; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-2; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-3; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-4; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-5; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-6; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-7; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-8; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946
  - Covered buggy stuck in a muddy rural road, T. K. Bruner pictured, ca. 1903. (N.76.9.10), PhC.42.Bx28.Unidentified.F4-9; Brimley, Herbert Hutchinson, 1861-1946